<?xml version="1.0"?>

<extensions>
	<details>
		<title lang="EN">Erland's plugins</title>
	</details>
	<plugins>
		<plugin name="AutoRepo" version="1.0" minTarget="7.3.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Auto Repositories</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Automatically makes all third party plugin repositories that are listed on the Logitech wiki site available through Extension Downloader. The plugin doesn't actually read the wiki page directly since that would open up a security hole, instead it reads the repositories from a list available on the erlandplugins Google Code project. New repostories added to the wiki page will be added after they have been checked so they provide serious plugins and not spam urls.</desc>
                        <creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
                        <email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-autorepo&amp;filename=AutoRepo-1.0.zip</url>
                        <sha>49b9837c681ca4d9339224f086fa68c7ccb9ccff</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Auto_Repositories_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="TrackStat" version="2.8" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
			<title lang="EN">TrackStat</title>
			<desc lang="EN">Store statistics such as rating, last played time and play counts so it survives a rescan and allows to to browse your library based on the statistic information. You can set the ratings via the Squeezebox player, CLI, Squeezebox Controller or web interface, ratings and statistic data can also be imported/exported from/to iTunes, Amarok and MusicIP Mixer. It also supports Dynamic Playlist plugin by adding dynamic playlists for all its statistics. Please note that TrackStat needs a bit more resources than small plugins and might also slow down startup of SqueezeCenter a bit, so you might get problems if you are running SqueezeCenter on slow hardware.</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4
			- Corrected so internet meta data is shown correctly on Now Playing screen if one of the TRACKSTAT title formats is used
			- Added possibility to request parameters from top rated albums and most played album playlist templates for SQL Playlist
			- Added predefiend SQL Playlist playlists for playing top rated or most played albums in a genre, artist or year
			- Improved logic releated to finding moved tracks on multi disk albums when a TrackStat backup is restored</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
			<url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-trackstat&amp;filename=TrackStat-2.8.zip</url>
			<sha>d1330f4c5747ed65bc2c1e86d97431d7fe2165ab</sha>
			<link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/TrackStat_plugin</link>
		</plugin>
		<plugin name="CustomBrowse" version="2.8" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Custom Browse</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to customize the structure, contents and sorting of the browse menus on the Squeezebox. A new browse menu is configured as a xml file containing the structure and SQL-statements. Please note that Custom Browse needs a bit more resources than small plugins and might also slow down startup of SqueezeCenter a bit, so you might get problems if you are running SqueezeCenter on slow hardware.</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for filtering "Random Albums" menu by genre
			- Corrected so accelerated scrolling works in Tags menu on the Controller
			- Corrected so track details menu works on the Controller if latest SqueezeCenter 7.4 is used
			- Added support for showing duplicate text rows in album lists on the Controller (for example showing artists for an album)
			- Corrected so "Play all" items isn't repeated and doesn't overwrite real items in long lists on Controller
			- Added support for showing album arts in Tags menu
			- Corrected some small bugs</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-custombrowse&amp;filename=CustomBrowse-2.8.zip</url>
                        <sha>7c67dc318c68d4b925d4d4fb5457297edc9d9e75</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Custom_Browse_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="CustomScan" version="2.6" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Custom Scan</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Make it easier to develop modules that retreive additional information about artist, album, tracks from somehere. If used together with Custom Browse plugin, the included scanning modules for LastFM and custom tags makes it possible to browse music by LastFM tags or by a custom tag.</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for numeric sorted tags in Dynamic Tags menu
			- Added support for completely disable scanning modules to avoid refresh operation if only import/export modules are used
			- Added support for virtual tags using regular expressions in Custom Tag scanning module (Tag mapping parameter)
			- Added support for selecting to sort by number instead alphabetically in some custom tag menus
			- Added support for showing duplicate text lines in album lists on Controller (for examples showing the artist for an album), requires Custom Browse 2.8 or later.
			- Added support for showing album arts in Dyanmic Tags menu, requires Custom Browse 2.8 or later</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-customscan&amp;filename=CustomScan-2.6.zip</url>
                        <sha>60e51583f832ebe6515f5481363b97cb51153785</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Custom_Scan_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="CustomSkip" version="2.3.2" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Custom Skip</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to skip tracks automatically in dynamic playlists. Makes it possible to skip tracks with low ratings, zapped tracks, short tracks and much more</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-customskip&amp;filename=CustomSkip-2.3.2.zip</url>
                        <sha>97bb9a80a1cc24c46e4aa6b0d79898bb33c4bc9d</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Custom_Skip_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="DynamicPlayList" version="2.7" minTarget="7.2.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Dynamic Playlist</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Make it easy to create dynamic playlists for your own plugin. You simply need to implement two methods in your own plugin which returns the playlists and the next tracks. Currently at least supported by SQL Playlist plugin, TrackStat plugin, SugarCube plugin, iTunes Party Shuffle plugins and builtin support for saved static playlists</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4
			- Added support for custom tag based Dynamic Playlist mixers</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-dynamicplaylist&amp;filename=DynamicPlayList-2.7.zip</url>
                        <sha>087471a37a44bfe6b2542b00ec4929581f8679ff</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Dynamic_Playlist_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="DatabaseQuery" version="2.1.2" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Database Query</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to define and execute custom SQL statements towards SqueezeCenter database. The result can be displayed in the browser or exported as CSV or XML files.</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4
			- Corrected some small bugs</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-databasequery&amp;filename=DatabaseQuery-2.1.2.zip</url>
                        <sha>ef05d5f00298cf4c1a1e1426f9176567e12034f9</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Database_Query_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="MultiLibrary" version="2.3.1" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Multi Library</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to divide your SqueezeCenter library into different sub libraries, requires Custom Browse plugin to be able to browse the sub libraries. Please note that Multi Library needs a bit more resources than small plugins and might also slow down startup of SqueezeCenter a bit, so you might get problems if you are running SqueezeCenter on slow hardware.</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4
			- Corrected so internet meta data is shown correctly on Now Playing screen if MULTILIBRARIES title format is used
			- Corrected some small bugs</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-multilibrary&amp;filename=MultiLibrary-2.3.1.zip</url>
                        <sha>4c18394463689af4a2ac9c68f77eb471274dc7ae</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Multi_Library_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="SQLPlayList" version="2.4" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">SQL Playlist</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Creates smart playlists based on SQL queries, its possible to create playlists similar to iTunes smart playlists if used together with ratings set with the TrackStat plugin. It requires Dynamic Playlist plugin</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4
			- Added support for requesting parameters from random albums playlist templates
			- Added predefined playlists for playing a random album in a genre, decade, artist, playlist or year
			- Corrected some small bugs</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-sqlplaylist&amp;filename=SQLPlayList-2.4.zip</url>
                        <sha>78736678bb157d1d8b15a2c080173e845f2f2a55</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/SQL_Playlist_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		<plugin name="TitleSwitcher" version="1.1.2" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Title Switcher</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to get text information on the player screen that switches between different kind of information, for example showing artist 5 seconds and album name 5 seconds. The plugin requires that the Music Information Screen(MusicInfoSCR) plugin is installed.</desc>
			<changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4</changes>
			<creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
			<email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-titleswitcher&amp;filename=TitleSwitcher-1.1.2.zip</url>
                        <sha>feaf935bfc3802ed3cea5919122f451f33ec81fc</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Title_Switcher_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
                <plugin name="TrackStatPlaylist" version="1.0.1" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">TrackStat Playlist</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to export the TrackStat statistics such as ratings and played tracks to static playlists. This is useful when you like to manually update ratings in for example J River Media Center based on a playlist that contains all 4 rated tracks. Please note that this plugin requires you to install both TrackStat and Custom Scan plugin.</desc>
                        <changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4</changes>
                        <creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
                        <email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-trackstatplaylist&amp;filename=TrackStatPlaylist-1.0.1.zip</url>
                        <sha>d23167c3c3eb0388428e0484f4ecdfaeb3b13918</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/TrackStat_Playlist_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
		 <plugin name="PlaylistGenerator" version="1.0.1" minTarget="7.1.0" maxTarget="*">
                        <title lang="EN">Playlist Generator</title>
                        <desc lang="EN">Makes it possible to generate static playlists based on information in SqueezeCenter database, such as ratings and played tracks. This is useful when you like to have a playlist as a .m3u file which you can export to other tools. This plugin works by itself but if you also install Custom Scan you will be able to re-generate all playlists automatically when you perform a rescan in SqueezeCenter.</desc>
                        <changes lang="EN">- Added support for SqueezeCenter 7.4</changes>
                        <creator>Erland Isaksson</creator>
                        <email>erland_i@hotmail.com</email>
                        <url>http://erland.isaksson.info/download/do/downloadapplication?name=slimserver-playlistgenerator&amp;filename=PlaylistGenerator-1.0.1.zip</url>
                        <sha>7ec594c94709065f0adbf9bdf5cf4513519911db</sha>
                        <link>http://wiki.slimdevices.com/index.php/Playlist_Generator_plugin</link>
                </plugin>
	</plugins>
</extensions>

